

Mohammad Jawhar

Phone: (+62) 82122265118

Address: St. Moritz Apartment, The Royal Suite Tower, Jakarta 11610

Email: mohamadjawhar@live.com

CAREER SUMMARY

Hospitlaity Executive in a Travel Job with overseas experience in the levant region, GCC Arabia & SE Asia. My extensive work background in hotel operations circulated around rooms division, Quality control, operation audit, pre – opening assesement, budget & forcast, profit & loss and interim hotel general manager.

Regional Operations Manager at Swiss Belhotel International regional office in Jakarta & Malaysia. Responsible in operating more than 15 hotels by raising the standards of hotels (products & services), providing operational assitance and assesing operational readiness for pre opening hotels and acting as interim hotel manager for hotels in transition enhancing corporate support for projects as directed. Reporting directly to the senior vice president of operations and development.

As Guest Lecturer and Hospitality Instructor Instruct students in their specilaised field of Front Office and Houskeeping which is practical in nature, provides theoritical instruction in service of the pretical skills and techniques that the students must subsequently master for a hospitality related profession.

EDUCATION

American University of Science & Technology

(2021-2022)

Teaching Diploma in Business Administration

Arts, Sciences & Technology University in Lebanon

(2016-2018)

Executive Masters in Business Administration

American University of Culture & Education

(2003-2006)

Bachelor degree in Hospitality Administration

WORK EXPERIENCE

Swiss-Belhotel International – Regional Office - Indonesia

(2018-Present)

Regional Operations Manager

(2019-2020)

Interim Hotel General Manager

(2018-2019)

Regional Operations Executive

SKILLS

Standard of Procedures

HCCP & Hygiene

Communication Skills

E-commerce

Learning & Development

Operational Audit

Teaching skills

Quality Control

Pre – Openings

Budget & Forcast

LANGAUGES

Arabic

English

ACTIVITIES

Travel

Sports

Reading

REFERENCES

Available Upon Request

University of Brawijaya - Indonesia (2021-Present)

Hospitality Guest Lecturer

Arts, Sciences & Technology University - Lebanon (2017-2018)

Hospitality Instructor

Inn & Go Kuwait Plaza Hotel - Kuwait (2016-2018)

Front Office Manager

Swiss Belhotel Plaza Kuwait - Kuwait (2012-2016)

Front Office Manager

Millennium Hotel Doha - Qatar (2010-2012)

Head Concierge

Golden Tulip Serenada Hotel - Lebanon (2010-2010)

Night Auditor

Le Duroy Boutique Hotel - Lebanon (2009-2010)

Night Auditor

Regency Hotel Kuwait - Kuwait (2009-2009)

Chief Concierge

Four Points By Sheraton - Kuwait (2006-2009)

Chief Concierge

Al Zahraa University Hospital - Lebanon (2005-2006)

Admission Officer

Le Meridian Commodore Hotel - Lebanon (2004-2005)

F&B Contoller

Crown Plaza Hotel - Lebanon (2004-2004)

Hospitality Trainee